http://www.stowers-institute.org/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Search form
Search
HomeAbout the InstituteJim and Virginia StowersLeadershipBoard of DirectorsScientific Advisory BoardResearch CampusQuick FactsAmerican CenturyBioMed Valley DiscoveriesOur LocationLiving in Kansas CityContact UsScientists & ResearchScientistsResearch AdvisorGenomics ScientistsCore LeadersCore CentersAutomation and PCR TechnologyComputational BiologyCytometryElectron MicroscopyGenome EngineeringHistologyImagingLab Animal ServicesMedia PreparationMicroscopyProteomicsReptile & AquaticsScreeningTissue CultureSequencing and Discovery GenomicsResearch WebsitesPublicationsEducationGraduate SchoolPostdoctoral ProgramMentoringScientific SupportGrants & FellowshipsPostdoctoral LifePostdoctoral AlumniApplyAffiliated PhD ProgramsOpen UniversityOur StudentsEligibilityAdmissionsRegistrationCommitteeRequirementsSkills EvaluationPolicies & GuidelinesContact UsIGPBS at KUMCCrossroadsActivitiesPast EventsCommitteeUseful LinksSummer ScholarsNews & MediaStowers NewsIn the mediaStowers Report 2019Stowers Report ArchiveVideoA Look in the LabEventsSeminarsWednesday LecturesPast Wednesday LecturesBIG IDEAS @ScienceStowersUpcoming LecturesPast LecturesSymposiaResearch ConferencesCareersCurrent OpeningsBenefits OverviewLiving In Kansas CitySupport UsBasic ResearchHope for LifeEndowmentDonateContact Us
Privacy Policy
The Stowers Institute for Medical Research values its donors, job applicants, volunteers and all online visitors (collectively, "Visitors") and is committed to respecting and protecting their privacy. It does not sell, trade or rent information it collects from them with other organizations or use that information to make mailings on behalf of other organizations. Within the Stowers Institute, we limit access to this information to circumstances that require such access.
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.
Information the Stowers Institute collects includes personal information that is voluntarily provided by Visitors, including electronically, and information that is publicly available. The types of personally identifiable information collected may include a Visitor's name, home, work and email address, telephone and fax number, credit card information, date of birth, gender, qualifications, educational and work history and expertise.
The Stowers Institute uses that information to accept donations and applications for employment; to inform our donors and friends about news from the Stowers Institute, upcoming events, and our fundraising needs; to thank donors; and to distribute receipts.
The Stowers Institute provides the opportunity to those donors who do not wish to be publicly acknowledged to be recognized anonymously.
We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or others’ rights, property, or safety.
The Stowers Institute may need to disclose personal information to trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you. We try to ensure that these entities do not use personal information for any other purpose, and that they have agreed to maintain the confidentiality and integrity of the information they obtain from us.
The Stowers Institute also collects certain traffic data information such as an online Visitor's IP address, domain server, type of computer and type of web browser. This is anonymous information that does not personally identify the Visitor but is helpful for purposes of improving the experience on our website.
We provide links from our websites to other websites that we believe may be of interest to our online Visitors. Please be aware that those sites may collect information. This policy does not apply to, and cannot control, those other websites.Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.stowers.org/termsYour Consent
By using our site, you consent to our website privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy Policy
This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes.Contacting Us
We will remove anyone who requests deletion from our mailing lists. If you wish to be removed or have any questions about our privacy policy, please email us at communications@stowers.org
(Last updated September, 2011.)
